A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Finance, 1986-1998
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Secretary of Finance Correspondence and Subject files, 1986-1998
The Library of Virginia
34593, 34974, 35256, 35871
40 cu. ft. (40 boxes)
Virginia. Secretary of Finance.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Secretary of Finance, 16 March 1994 [Accession 34593]; Transferred from the Secretary of Finance, 16 October 1995 [Accession 34974]; Transferred from the Secretary of Finance, 1 October 1996 [Accession 35256]; and Transferred from the Secretary of Finance, 1998 [Accession 35871]
Biographical Information
Stuart W. Connock was appointed Secretary of Finance in 1984 by Governor Charles Robb and was reappointed in 1986 by Governor Gerald Baliles and served until his retirement in 1989. Paul W. Timmreck was appointed Secretary by Governor Douglas Wilder in January 1990 and was reappointed by Governor George Allen in 1994. Upon Timmreck's resignation in July 1996, Governor Allen appointed Ronald L. Tillett. Tillet was reappointed by Governor James Gilmore in 1998 and resigned in June 2001. Tillett's assistant, John W. Forbes, replaced him in July 2001 and served until the end of the Gilmore administration in January 2002.
Scope and Content
This series contains correspondence and subject files relating to the fiscal management of the state government agencies. The majority of correspondence files are organized by Secretary and chronologically thereunder. Some correspondence is organized by subject or name of its recipient. The subject files are organized by headings. The files may include reports memoranda, budgetary bills presentations and speeches related to state financial activities, cost containment, state taxation, decentralization and other fiscal matters.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Correspondence and subject files, 1986-1994 [Accession 34593]
Series II: Correspondence and subject files, 1986-1994 [Accession 34974]
Series III: Correspondence and subject files, 1988-1994 [Accession 35256]
Series IV: Correspondence and subject files, 1994-1998 [Accession 35871]
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 34593], 1986-1994, Extent: 24 cu. ft. (24 boxes). (Box 1-24)
  - General Assembly Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1990 June 16 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1990 September 17 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1990 October 15 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1990 December 3 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1991 April 1 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1991 May 20 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1991 June 17 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1991 July 15 (Box 1)
  - House Appropriation Committee Meetings, 1991 October 21 (Box 1)
  - Joint meetings, 1989 August 28 (Box 1)
  - Joint meetings, 1989 December 18 (Box 1)
  - Joint meetings, 1990 February 15 (Box 1)
  - Joint meetings, 1990 August 17 (Box 1)
  - Joint meetings, 1990 December 17 (Box 1)
  - Health Care Commission files, 1991 June 11 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, 1991 July 16 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, 1991 August 6 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, Cost Containment Subcommittee, 1990 July 18 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, Cost Containment Subcommittee, 1990 September 26 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, Cost Containment Subcommittee, 1990 October 23 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, Cost Containment Subcommittee, 1990 November 26 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, Cost Containment Subcommittee, 1990 December 17 (Box 2)
  - Health Care Commission files, Cost Containment Subcommittee, 1991 January 14 (Box 2)
  - Tobacco Row (Box 2)
  - Child Care Credit, 1989 (Box 3)
  - City of Richmond Real Estate Taxes, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Tax Compliance Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Federal Repeal of Estate Tax, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Tax-Food Stamps, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Food Credit, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Income Tax Withholding Study, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Individual Income Tax Processing Plan, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Local Tax Authority (Box 3)
  - Nongame Wildlife Contribution (Box 3)
  - Prompt Pay (Box 3)
  - Sales Tax Inc., Implementation, HB 2, Special Session, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Tax Space Needs (Box 3)
  - Technical Corrections Act of 1988 (Box 3)
  - Tax of Daily Rental Equipment, 1988 (Box 3)
  - VIT Pending Court Case (Box 3)
  - Senate Finance Committee Meetings, 1990 June 22 (Box 3)
  - Senate Finance Committee Meetings, 1990 September 28 (Box 3)
  - Senate Finance Committee Meetings, 1990 October 19 (Box 3)
  - Senate Finance Committee Meetings, 1990 November 16 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal Year 1990 Year End Close (Box 3)
  - Income Tax Consultant Services, Dept. of Accounts (Box 3)
  - Interest Earnings Non General Fund (Box 3)
  - Licensing Setoff Study (Box 3)
  - State Aid to Localities (Box 3)
  - State Aid Intercept (Box 3)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation, Statewide Elected Leadership, 1990 March 5 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation, 1989 January 13 (Box 3)
  - Legislative Proposals, Local Option Income Tax, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Amnesty, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Recordation Tax, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Tax Reform, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Taxation Background, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Mail Order Tax, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Corporate Income Tax, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Corporate Income Tax, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Non prescription Drugs, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Estate Tax, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Local Income Tax, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, TVA Payment Distribution, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, ACRS, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Treasury Background, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Route 28, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, 9 (c) Issuance, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, 9 (d) Revenue Bond, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, SNAP, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Escheat, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Unclaimed Property, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Treasury Board Authority to Issue Debt, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Investment of Institutional Funds, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Firearm Transaction Fees Act, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Park Facilities, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, June Collection Budget Language, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, General Assembly Miscellaneous Memos, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Proposals, Background Information, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, State Internal Audit Sunset Repeal, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Powers and Duties of APA, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Legislative Studies, Proposals, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Legislative Initiatives, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Background materials, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, DPB Background, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, DOA Background, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Taxation Background, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, EFT, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Age Deduction, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Emergency Age Subtraction, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Sales Tax Exemption for Physicians-Controlled Drugs, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Criminal Tax Penalties, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Administration of Tax System, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Shared Provider, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Deferral Legislation, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Treasury Background, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, 9 (c) Issuance, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, VPBA, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Merge Annual Reports, DOA and Treasury, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Deposit of Securities for Insurance Companies, HMO's, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Unclaimed Property, Penalties and Interest, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, State Deposit Procedures, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Unclaimed Property Act, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Proposals, Secrecy of Information, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Monthly Revenue Data, 1990 July-1992 June (Box 6)
  - Financial Agencies Project Streamline Proposals, Phases I and II (Box 7)
  - Finance Agencies' Initiatives, 1990-1994 (Box 8)
  - Initiatives Notebook (Box 8)
  - Memos to and from Governor's Office, 1990-1992 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence to General Assembly, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Bill Reviews, Special Session II, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Patron Thank you letters, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Bill Reviews, Memos, 1991 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly Bill Reviews Miscellaneous Memos, 1992 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly Bill Reviews, House Bills, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), Meeting files, 1991 February 15 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), Meeting files, 1991 June 25 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), Meeting files, 1991 October 11 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), Meeting files, 1992 February 5 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), Meeting files, 1992 June 30 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), Meeting files, 1992 October 23 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE), Meeting files, 1991 July 31 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE), Meeting files, 1991 November 26 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE), Meeting files, 1992 July 31 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE), Meeting files, 1992 November 18 (Box 10)
  - General Assembly Bill Reviews, Senate Bills, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1990 February 15 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1990 August 13 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1990 September 26 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1990 November 9 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1990 December 12 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1991 February 1 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1991 August 13 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1991 September 18 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1991 October 16 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1991 November 15 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1991 December 10 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1992 February 13 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1992 August 11 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council (GEAC), Meeting files, 1992 December 1 (Box 11)
  - Monthly Revenue Data, Fiscal year 1990 (Box 11)
  - National Tax Administrators (NTA), 84th Annual Conference, 1991 November 10-13 (Box 11)
  - Finance Organization Study (Box 12)
  - HJR 373, Higher Education Financing, 1989 (Box 12)
  - HJR 373, Commission Studying Alternative Financing for Colleges and Universities (Box 12)
  - Dept. of State Internal Auditor Duties Study, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Decentralization of Higher Education (Local Fund Accounts Study) (Box 12)
  - Commercial Space Group, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Administrative Law Judge Panel and Establishment of Uniform Rules (Box 12)
  - Secretary of Finance Studies, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Accounts Receivable Study, Licensing Setoff, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - SJR 198, Combined Sewer Overflow Study (Box 13)
  - Criminal Penalty Provision Study (Box 13)
  - Edward J. Mazur, Comptroller (Box 13)
  - Agency Based Accounting (Box 13)
  - Accounts APA Report Work plans (Box 13)
  - Comptroller's Annual Report Background, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
  - Comptroller's Debt Setoff Study, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Decentralization of Public Records (Box 13)
  - Direct Deposit (Box 13)
  - Directives, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
  - DOA-DPB Task Force> (Box 13)
  - EEO-AA Plan (Box 13)
  - Goals and Objectives (Box 13)
  - Indirect Cost Recoveries (Box 13)
  - Interlining Study (Railroad Transportation) (Box 13)
  - Internal Audit Department, 1987 (Box 13)
  - DOA Miscellaneous Correspondence and Memos (Box 13)
  - Monthly Management Reports (Box 13)
  - Office of Management and Budget (Box 13)
  - Personnel (Box 13)
  - Accounts, Projected Cash Requirements (Box 14)
  - Prompt Pay Compliance (Box 14)
  - Quarterly Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance (Box 14)
  - Quarterly Report on Revenue Growth Percent Analysis (Box 14)
  - Accounts Receivable (Box 14)
  - Comptroller's Scorecard (Box 14)
  - State Agency Group Luncheon Expense Reimbursement Policy (Box 14)
  - Travel charge cards> (Box 14)
  - Travel reimbursement (Box 14)
  - Taxation, Tax Amnesty Program (Box 14)
  - Annual report, Taxation (Box 14)
  - APA Audit, Taxation (Box 14)
  - Arlington County, R, F, & P Railroad Company (Box 14)
  - Budget (Box 14)
  - Cigarette Tax (Box 14)
  - Consumer Use Tax (Box 14)
  - Desert Shield, Desert Storm (Box 14)
  - Electronic Funds Transfer (Box 14)
  - EEO-AA Plan (Box 14)
  - 4-R Act (Box 14)
  - Hercules (Box 14)
  - Income tax (Box 14)
  - Income tax processing (Box 14)
  - Internal audit (Box 14)
  - Legislation (Box 14)
  - Maryland Commission on State Tax, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Mapping Function (Box 14)
  - National Issues Tracking Report (Box 14)
  - Economy watch, Monthly> (Box 15)
  - Revenue forecasting (Box 15)
  - Quarterly tracking report (Box 15)
  - Non prescription drugs (Box 15)
  - Roy Pearson Projects (Box 15)
  - Sales tax (Box 15)
  - Set-off Debt Collection Act (Box 15)
  - Tax reform implementation (Box 15)
  - Treasury Guidelines for Selection of Investment Bankers, 1987 (Box 15)
  - State Parks Financing, Virginia Public Building Authority, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Unclaimed Property Being Held by the Federal Government, 1987 (Box 15)
  - VPBA meeting, 1987 December 3 (Box 15)
  - VPBA Publication, Tax Exempt Line of Credit (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, Decision Briefs, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, Guidelines for HB 1162, Delegation of Duties (Box 15)
  - Emergency Assistance Funds, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Minority Purchasing Reports (Box 15)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1988 (Box 15)
  - NASBO, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Comptroller's Annual Report, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Annual report, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Edward Mazur, 1988 (Box 16)
  - CARS II, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Debt Collection Act, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Direct Deposit of Employee Pay, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Directives, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Due Date Monitoring Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - DOA Affirmative Action Statistics, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Fixed Asset Accounting Control (Box 16)
  - Indirect Cost Recoveries, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
  - DOA-DIT, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
  - Minority Purchasing Reports (Box 16)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Prompt Pay Compliance, 1988-1990 (Box 16)
  - Accounts Receivable, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
  - Telecommunications Study, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Taxation APA Audits, 1986-1990 (Box 17)
  - Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 17)
  - Internal Audit Function, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Meeting with Forst, 1988 October (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
  - Personnel, 1986-1990 (Box 17)
  - Emergency Regulations ACRS Phase Out, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Tax Refund Processing, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Regulations, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Public Documents, 1988 September (Box 17)
  - Alice Handy, Treasurer (Box 17)
  - William Wiley, Treasurer (Box 17)
  - AOA Audit, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Treasury, Annual Report, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Deposit Requirements for State Funds, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Interfund Borrowing, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence, Treasury, 1987 (Box 17)
  - State Treasurer Appointment, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Deputy Treasurer Position (Box 17)
  - Treasury Personnel (Box 17)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, Meetings, 1988 November 21 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, Meetings, 1989 December 6 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, Meetings, 1990 November 20 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, Meetings, 1988 October 24 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, Meetings, 1989 October 17 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, Meetings, 1990 October 11 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1988 February 11 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1988 August 22 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1988 December 13 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1989 August 22 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1989 November 22 (Box 18)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1989 December 12 (Box 18)
  - General Fund Revenue Forecast Fiscal Years, 1990 (Box 18)
  - General Fund Revenue Forecast Fiscal Years, 1991 (Box 18)
  - General Fund Revenue Forecast Fiscal Years, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Monthly Revenue Data, 1988 July-1989 June (Box 18)
  - Year End Close, 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - Joint House Appropriation, House Finance, Senate Finance Committees Meetings, 1987 August 24 (Box 19)
  - Joint House Appropriation, House Finance, Senate Finance Committees Meetings, 1987 December 18 (Box 19)
  - Joint House Appropriation, House Finance, Senate Finance Committees Meetings, 1988 August 21 (Box 19)
  - Joint House Appropriation, House Finance, Senate Finance Committees Meetings, 1988 December 19 (Box 19)
  - Finance Secretariat, Agenda, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Agenda, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Secretary of Finance, APA Reports (Box 19)
  - AA, EEO, Secretary of Finance (Box 19)
  - Appointments by Governor, Finance Boards, Commissions, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Appointments by Governor, Recommended by Secretary of Finance, 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Connock Agenda, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Agenda, Finance, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
  - Audits, Secretary of Finance, 1987-1990 (Box 19)
  - Air Travel Card (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1990 October 25 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1990 November 20 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1990 December 19 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1991 October 21 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 March 20
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 April 9 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 May 13 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 June 5 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 July 8 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 August 5 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 September 25 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 October 14 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 November 23 (Box 19)
  - Agency Head Meetings, 1992 December 9 (Box 19)
  - Barker, Deborah (Box 19)
  - Dr. John Bowman Contract Personnel Services, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Finance Budget, 1984-1986 (Box 19)
  - Financial Proposals, 1988-1990 (Box 19)
  - Combined Virginia Campaign, 1989 August-1993 December (Box 19)
  - Statement of Economic Interests> (Box 20)
  - Decorating, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Finance Agencies Contingency Plans (Box 20)
  - Finance Disclosures, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Monthly Financial Statements, 1989 June-1992 April (Box 20)
  - Monthly Financial Statements, 1988 June-1989 May (Box 20)
  - Finance Financial (Year End) Statements, 1984-1992 (Box 20)
  - Insurance Payments (Box 20)
  - Major Issues for Finance, 1986-1988 (Box 20)
  - Major Issues for Finance, 1988-1989 (Box 20)
  - Membership Dues (Box 20)
  - Memos to Finance Agency Heads (Box 20)
  - Office move, Furniture (Box 20)
  - Secretary of Finance Parking (Box 20)
  - Support Services, 1989-1992 (Box 20)
  - Subscriptions> (Box 20)
  - Supply orders (Box 20)
  - Surplus Property (Box 20)
  - Telecommunications (Box 20)
  - Temporary Services Contracts (Box 20)
  - United Way, 1987-1993 (Box 20)
  - Savings Bonds, 1989-1992 (Box 20)
  - Treasurer, Eddie N. Moore, Jr. (Box 21)
  - AA, EEO Plan, 1991 (Box 21)
  - APA Comments, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Budget, 1989-1992 (Box 21)
  - Bonded Debt, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Bond Rating Agencies Meetings, 1990 May-November (Box 21)
  - Bond Rating Agencies Meetings, 1990 November (Box 21)
  - Bond Rating Agencies Meetings, 1991 February 8 (Box 21)
  - Bond Rating Agencies Meetings, 1991 September 27-28 (Box 21)
  - Bond Rating Agencies Meetings, 1992 March 26 (Box 21)
  - Bond Rating Agencies Meetings, 1992 September 17-18 (Box 21)
  - 9c Bond Issuance, Authorization, 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Debt Calendars (Box 21)
  - Financial Feasibility Study (Box 21)
  - Internal Audit Program (Box 21)
  - Council on Local Debt, 1990-1992 (Box 21)
  - Misc. Correspondence, Treasury, 1991-1993 (Box 21)
  - Missing checks (Box 21)
  - Monthly Cash Forecast Report (Box 21)
  - Monthly Management Report, 1990 (Box 21)
  - College Savings Bond Program (Box 21)
  - Treasury Board, 1989-1991 (Box 21)
  - Virginia College Building Authority, Bond Sales (Box 21)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority, Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority, Legislation, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Public School Authority, Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget Director, Karen F. Washabau (Box 21)
  - Appropriations Act (Box 21)
  - Budget, 1992-1994 (Box 21)
  - Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Budget bills (Box 21)
  - Budget tabloid (Box 21)
  - Capital Outlay, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Carry-Over Requests, 1987-1988 (Box 21)
  - Higher Education Equipment Trust Fund (Box 21)
  - Matching Funds Certification, 1990-1992 (Box 22)
  - Dept. Planning and Budget, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Dept. Planning and Budget, Personnel, 1988-1992 (Box 22)
  - Pre Legislative Proposals, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Budget Reductions, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
  - Reports to Money Committees Transfer to Economic Contingency Fund (Box 22)
  - Required Studies, 1993 (Box 22)
  - John Huston, State Internal Auditor (Box 22)
  - Biennial Report, 1991 (Box 22)
  - DSIA Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - Misc. Correspondence, DSIA, 1991-1993 (Box 22)
  - DSIA, Personnel (Box 22)
  - Treasury Loans, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - Fiscal Outlook, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Taxation of Services, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - Federal Budget, 1990-1993 (Box 22)
  - VRS Assets Valuation, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Budget Development, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Master Plan Capital Square and Main Street Station, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Japanese Delegation, 1993 November (Box 23)
  - Governor's Press Breakfast (Box 23)
  - Governor's Fellows, 1988-1993 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office Automation Commission, 1990 (Box 23)
  - GMU Land Transaction, 1989 (Box 23)
  - GASB Accounting Standards Changes (Box 23)
  - 4-H Extension (Box 23)
  - Freedom of Information, 1988-1989 (Box 23)
  - Federation of Tax Administrators, 1989-1993 (Box 23)
  - Federal Banking Reform Legislation, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Federal Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 23)
  - Executive Orders, 1990-1992 (Box 23)
  - Delegation of Authority (Box 23)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation, 1986-1990 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation, 1991 January 25 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation, 1992 February 7 (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Council of State Governments, 1989-1992 (Box 24)